topicsinenglish.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Topics in English

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by **Put your e-mail here.**

 **topicsinenglish.com@gmail.com**

At **[topics in english](https://topicsinenglish.com/)** ** ** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by **[topics in english](https://topicsinenglish.com/) **and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, **[topics in english](https://topicsinenglish.com/)** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Comments

When visitors leave their comments on the site, we collect the data described in the feedback form, as well as the visitor’s IP address and the user’s browser proxy series to help detect spam.

Media

If you upload images to a website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS). Site visitors can download and extract any site data from images on the website.

Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site, you can enable your name, email address, and website to be saved in your cookies. These are for your convenience so you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and are signed in to this site, we’ll set up a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts these files. This cookie does not contain any personal data and is disposed of when you close your browser.

When you sign in, we also configure several cookies to store your login information and display options. Cookies for login information remain for two days, while the display option cookies remain for a year. Your sign-in will continue for two weeks when you choose to “Remember me” and if you sign out of your account, your login cookies will be deleted.

An additional cookie will be saved to your browser if you edit or publish an article. This file does not contain any personal data, but it refers to the article ID you edited. It will expire one day later.

Content included from other websites

Articles on this site may contain content that is included (for example: videos, images, articles, etc.). The embedded content from other Web sites behaves in exactly the same way as if the visitor visited the other site.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, integrate third party third party tracking, and monitor your interaction with this embedded content, including tracking your interaction with embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that site.

How long do we keep your data?

If you leave a comment, your comment and metadata will be kept indefinitely. This is so that we can recognize and approve any consecutive comments automatically rather than keeping them in the review queue for approval.

For users who have registered on our site (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can view, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except that they can not change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit this information.

What are your rights to your data

If you have an account on this site, or leave comments, you can request a file to be exported from the personal data we hold about you, including any data you provide us. You can also request to delete any personal data we keep about you. This does not include any data that we are obliged to maintain for administrative, legal or security purposes.

Where we send your data

Visitor comments can be verified through the spam detection service automatically.

Cookies and Web Beacons

[ **topics in english**](https://topicsinenglish.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **[topics in english](https://topicsinenglish.com/)**.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to **[topics in english](https://topicsinenglish.com/) **and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [**topics in english**](https://topicsinenglish.com/) ** **  send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[ **topics in english**](https://topicsinenglish.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **[topics in english](https://topicsinenglish.com/)**‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites
